<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animals</string>
    
    <string name="lion">Lion</string>
    <string name="tiger">Tiger</string>
    <string name="cheetah">Cheetah</string>
    <string name="wolf">Wolf</string>
    <string name="hyena">Hyena</string>
    <string name="fox">Fox</string>
    <string name="bear">Bear</string>
    <string name="elephant">Elephant</string>
    <string name="panda">Panda</string>
    <string name="horse">Horse</string>
    <string name="zebra">Zebra</string>
    <string name="buffalo">Buffalo</string>
    <string name="giraffe">Giraffe</string>
    <string name="gorilla">Gorilla</string>
    <string name="chimpanzee">Chimpanzee</string>
    <string name="monkey">Monkey</string>
    <string name="pig">Pig</string>
    <string name="deer">Deer</string>
    <string name="sheep">Sheep</string>
    <string name="raccoon">Raccoon</string>
    <string name="koala">Koala</string>
    <string name="sloth">Sloth</string>
    <string name="rabbit">Rabbit</string>
    <string name="meerkat">Meerkat</string>
    <string name="rat">Rat</string>

    <string name="eagle">Eagle</string>
    <string name="peacock">Peacock</string>
    <string name="woodpecker">Woodpecker</string>

    <string name="crocodile">Crocodile</string>
    <string name="tortoise">Tortoise</string>






    <string name="about_lion">The king of the jungle is a large cat of the genus Panthera, native to Africa and India.
 It has a muscular, broad-chested body; a short, rounded head; round ears; and a hairy tuft
 at the end of its tail.</string>
    <string name="about_tiger">The tiger is the largest living cat species and a member of the genus Panthera native to Asia .
 It has a powerful, muscular body with a large head and paws, a long tail, and orange fur with black,
 mostly vertical stripes.</string>
    <string name="about_cheetah">The cheetah is a large cat and the fastest land animal. It has a tawny to creamy white or pale
 buff fur that is marked with evenly spaced, solid black spots. The head is small and rounded, with a
 short snout and black tear-like facial streaks.The cheetah\'s unique body structure: flexible spine,
 semi-retractable claws, long legs and tail allow it to achieve the unbelievable top speed of 110
 km/hr (70 mph). The cheetah\'s body is narrow and lightweight with long slender limbs. Specialized
 muscles allow for a greater swing to the limbs increasing acceleration.
</string>
    <string name="about_wolf">Gray wolves have long legs that are well adapted to running, allowing them to move fast and travel
 far in search of food, and large skulls and jaws that are well suited to catching and feeding on
 large mammals. Wolves also have keen senses of smell, hearing and vision, which they use to detect
 prey and one another.</string>
    <string name="about_hyena">Hyenas or hyaenas are feliform carnivoran mammals belonging to the family Hyaenidae.It has a large
 head with a long, thick, muscular neck and powerful jaws that give the hyena the strongest bite of
 any mammal. Its front legs are longer than its back legs, giving the hyena a profile somewhat like
 that of a wildebeest or bison. The spotted hyena\'s paws have four toes with non-retractable claws.</string>
    <string name="about_fox">Foxes are small-to-medium-sized omnivorous mammals belonging to several genera of the family
 Canidae. They have a flattened skull; upright, triangular ears; a pointed, slightly upturned snout;
 and a long, bushy tail.</string>
    <string name="about_bear">Adult bears present an imposing physical presence. All species have broad heads, extended jaws,
 massive frames, heavy paws, powerful claws, and shaggy coats. The polar bear is white; most other
 types are black, brown, or cinnamon in color. Bears vary in size according to their species.
</string>
    <string name="about_elephant">Elephants are the largest living land animals.Distinctive features of elephants include a long
 proboscis called a trunk, tusks, large ear flaps, pillar-like legs, and tough but sensitive grey skin.
 The trunk is prehensile, bringing food and water to the mouth and grasping objects.</string>
    <string name="about_panda">The giant panda, also known as the panda bear or simply panda, is a bear species endemic to China.
 It is characterised by its black-and-white coat and rotund body. The name "giant panda" is sometimes
 used to distinguish it from the red panda, a neighboring musteloid. Adult individuals average 100 to
 115 kg (220 to 254 lb), and are typically 1.2 to 1.9 m (3 ft 11 in to 6 ft 3 in) long.The fur is
 white, with black patches around the eyes, ears, legs and shoulders. A thumb is visible on the bear\'s
 forepaw, which helps in holding bamboo in place for feeding.</string>
    <string name="about_horse">Horses have oval-shaped hooves, long tails,short hair, long slender legs, muscular and deep torso
 build, long thick necks, and large elongated heads. The mane is a region of coarse hairs, which
 extends along the dorsal side of the neck in both domestic and wild species.</string>
    <string name="about_zebra">Zebras are known for their black and white stripes. The stripes start as brown streaks and
 darken to black as the zebra ages. The stripes are unique to each zebra.Zebras are members of
 the horse family and are sturdy, spirited animals with excellent hearing and eyesight. They can run
 up to 35 miles per hour and have a powerful kick that can seriously injure a predator.
 Zebras walk, trot, canter, and gallop like horses, but not as quickly. </string>
    <string name="about_buffalo">African buffalo and Asian water buffalo have horns that are triangular-shaped in cross-section.
 In the African buffalo\'s skull, the vomer and palatine bones remain separate,
 while in the water buffalo they are fused. Stout legs to support its ox-like body.</string>
    <string name="about_giraffe">The giraffe is the tallest of all mammals. It reaches an overall height of 18 ft (5.5 m) or more.
 The legs and neck are extremely long. The giraffe has a short body, a tufted tail, a short mane,
 and short skin-covered horns.</string>
    <string name="about_gorilla">The largest of the great apes, gorillas are stocky animals with broad chests and shoulders, large,
 human-like hands, and small eyes set into hairless faces.Gorillas are herbivorous.</string>
    <string name="about_chimpanzee">The chimpanzee, also simply known as the chimp, is a species of great ape native to the forests and
 savannahs of tropical Africa. The characteristic chimpanzee shape includes arms that extend beyond
 the knees, opposable thumbs, and a prominent mouth. The skin on the face, ears, palms, and soles of
 the feet is bare, and the rest of the body is covered with brown to black hair.</string>
    <string name="about_monkey">Most species are arboreal, using all four limbs to leap from tree to tree. They can sit upright
 and stand erect. Most species run along branches rather than swinging arm over arm like the apes.
 Monkeys are highly social omnivores, organized in clans as large as several hundred individuals headed
 by an old male.</string>
    <string name="about_pig">Wild boar have stocky, powerful bodies with a double layer of grey-brown fur – the top layer harsh,
 bristly hair; the under layer much softer. Mature males have tusks that protrude from the mouth.
 Piglets are a lighter ginger-brown, with stripes on their coat for camouflage.</string>
    <string name="about_deer">A deer or true deer is a hoofed ruminant ungulate of the family Cervidae.They typically have a
 compact body, short tail, and long, slender ears. They shed their antlers each year, and new ones
 grow in.Deer feed on grass, twigs, bark, and shoots.
</string>
    <string name="about_sheep">Most wild sheep are hardy animals with coats of both hair and wool to keep them warm in cold
 environments. Many are equipped with large, curling horns on the side of their head, which rams
 use to challenge would-be rivals and display dominance.</string>
    <string name="about_raccoon">Common Raccoons are stocky animals with short legs and small, rounded ears. Their fur is gray,
 with dark black markings around their eyes, and black bands on their tail. Their belly and muzzle
 are lighter colored while the feet are darker gray. Raccoons have coarse, medium-length fur and a
 very bushy tail.</string>
    <string name="about_koala">The koala, sometimes called the koala bear, is an arboreal herbivorous marsupial native to Australia.
Virtually tailless, the body is stout and gray, with a pale yellow or cream-coloured chest and
mottling on the rump. The broad face has a wide, rounded, leathery nose, small yellow eyes, and big
fluffy ears. </string>
    <string name="about_sloth">Sloths are a Neotropical group of xenarthran mammals.Sloths live in the tropical forests of Central
 and South America. With their long arms and shaggy fur, they resemble monkeys, but they are actually
 related to armadillos and anteaters.</string>
    <string name="about_rabbit">)Rabbits are small mammals in the family Leporidae.Rabbits are small, furry mammals with long ears,
 short fluffy tails, and strong, large hind legs. They have 2 pairs of sharp incisors (front teeth),
 one pair on top and one pair on the bottom. They also have 2 peg teeth behind the top incisors.
</string>
    <string name="about_meerkat">The meerkat or suricate is a small mongoose found in southern Africa. It is characterised by a
 broad head, large eyes, a pointed snout, long legs, a thin tapering tail, and a brindled coat pattern.
 The head-and-body length is around 24–35 cm, and the weight is typically between 0.62 and 0.97 kg.
</string>
    <string name="about_rat">Rattus is a genus of muroid rodents, all typically called rats.Rats have coarse fur that is usually
 dark grey or brown on the backside and light grey or brown on the underside. Rats can grow up to 10
 inches (25 cm) in body length. The tail is usually the same length as the body and can be pink or
 brown in color, but the tail always lacks fur.</string>

    <string name="about_eagle">Eagles are large, powerfully-built birds of prey, with heavy heads and beaks.Eagles are known
 for not giving up to the size or strength of their prey.Eagles have the sharpest visual acuity of any
 animal, which is due to their unique eye structure and visual principles.Eagles are the only birds
 that seem to get excited during storms, using the wind to soar to greater heights while other birds
 seek shelter.</string>
    <string name="about_peacock">Peafowl are known for their colorful and vibrant train of feathers and their elaborate mating
 displays. A male peafowl, or peacock, will fan out its feathers and rattle them to attract a peahen.
 Peafowls will also fan out their feathers to ward off predators. Mating season typically occurs
 during the monsoon season.</string>
    <string name="about_woodpecker">Woodpeckers are part of the bird family Picidae, which also includes the piculets, wrynecks and
 sapsuckers.Woodpeckers have strong bills that they use for drilling and drumming on trees, and long,
 sticky tongues for extracting food (insects and larvae). Woodpecker bills are typically longer,
 sharper, and stronger than the bills of piculets and wrynecks, but their morphology is very similar.
</string>

    <string name="about_crocodile">Crocodiles or true crocodiles are large semiaquatic reptiles that live throughout the tropics in
 Africa, Asia, the Americas and Australia.Crocodiles have powerful jaws with many conical teeth and
 short legs with clawed webbed toes. They share a unique body form that allows the eyes, ears, and
 nostrils to be above the water surface while most of the animal is hidden below. The tail is long
 and massive, and the skin is thick and plated.
</string>
    <string name="about_tortoise">Tortoises are reptiles of the family Testudinidae of the order Testudines. Like other turtles,
 tortoises have a shell to protect from predation and other threats.Tortoises have short, thick feet
 like those of an elephant\'s while turtles have webbed feet for swimming. A tortoise\'s shell is
 heavier and more rounded while a turtle\'s shell is lighter and flat. Tortoises are often loners.
 Tortoises are experts at getting all the water and nutrients they need from what they eat.</string>








</resources>